thelettertwo.com 2004-12-04

# TheLetterTwo.com :: Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting [thelettertwo.com](http://www.thelettertwo.com/). We understand the huge importance of customer privacy and want you to know what information is collected and how it will be used, if collected. 

**Information You Provide Us and How It's Used**  
Currently, there is _no_ information that is being collected through this site that will link to you, the user, in any way. Essentially, the only information that is being collected are the web traffic statistics and they are non-identifiable. Should that change, the updated policy can be found here.

**Disclosing information to outside parties**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. 

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**  
In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work). 

**Children's Privacy**  
Our web site is directed to a general audience. We do not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from children on our site.

**Online Policy Only**  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Consenting to the privacy policy**  
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to our policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. This policy was last modified on June 07, 2004.

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or the practices of our web site, you can [contact us](mailto:kyeung@thelettertwo.com).
